<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xml:base="http://www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk"  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
<channel>
 <title>Online Players Association .CO.UK</title>
 <link>http://www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk</link>
 <description>Online Players Association is an online casino and casino games portal for serious players.  Our online casino reviews are unbiased.  Our casino game articles are instructive.  Our gambling blog is entertaining.  Our exclusive casino bonuses are generous.  We are a gaming site operated by players, for players, and as such, take the interests and needs of the real gambling fan in hand.  Honesty, integrity, information.  That is our promise to you.  </description>
 <language>en</language>
<item>
 <title>Introduction to Online Video Poker</title>
 <link>http://www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk/casino/games/video-poker.html</link>
 <description>&lt;img src=&quot;/sites/onlineplayersassociation.co.uk/files/video-poker.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Video poker&quot; title=&quot;Video poker&quot; width=&quot;310&quot; height=&quot;200&quot; class=&quot;bigimage&quot; /&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;full_text&quot;&gt;The Video Poker era began back in 1970 when Dale Electronics developed the video poker machine. Although the public had some scepticism regarding the game, it was introduced shortly thereafter into land casino parlours, including those on the strip in Las Vegas, Nevada. The initial attempts to attract customers were not successful, because the machine failed to any appreciable degree to simulate the poker play at tables.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Video Poker - Grows on the Public&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;br&gt;
The game of Video Poker grew in popularity as people felt comfortable in the one-on-one contest with the machine, as opposed to playing poker in a group around a poker table, a much more intimidating environment. However, it was not until the Internet came of age that video poker really exploded upon the scene worldwide.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
As the trust grew in the online casino industry, gaming portals such as the Online Players Association exerted greater control over their affiliated operators. When the public realised that the online gambling industry was regulating itself through the Online Players Association, players flocked to the online casinos in order to play Video Poker. Why wouldn’t they prefer to play online? The online player can choose when, where and all other conditions of play. Patrons are guaranteed that the affiliates of the OPA are inspected every month for consistency and honesty in play and payoff percentages. With these guarantees, it is no wonder that one of the affiliated gambling sites, www.casinotropez.com, was named the Online Casino of the Year by Online Casino Magazine.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Video Poker - Available for Play at the Best Casinos&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Video Poker is a game that allows you to control the outcome. Once you’ve received your initial hand of 5 cards, the outcome of the game rests in your hands. You are free to discard none, any or all of the cards you were dealt. You’ll appreciate the fact that, no matter what type of video poker game you play, there are set payoffs for certain hands. For example, in Jacks or Better Poker, a pair of Jacks or better is a breakeven bet. In other words, if you bet 5 coins and the outcome of the game is a pair of Kings, you get back your initial bet, or 5 coins. There are a variety of Video Poker games available for play. You can choose among: Jacks or Better; Jacks or Better Bonus; Deuces Wild; Jacks or Better Double Bonus; Double Double Bonus; Joker Wild; Double Joker Wild; Aces and Faces and other varieties of  Video Poker.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Online casinos affiliated with OPA offer free games and instructions in the play of the different varieties of Video Poker. Visit www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk/ and review their recommendations for the best online casino Video Poker sites. Then come and join the fun.&lt;/div&gt;</description>
 <category domain="http://www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk/taxonomy/term/173">Video Poker</category>
 <category domain="http://www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk/taxonomy/term/264">show in block</category>
 <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2009 11:29:36 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>playtech</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">1997 at http://www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk</guid>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Introduction to Online Roulette</title>
 <link>http://www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk/casino/games/roulette.html</link>
 <description>&lt;img src=&quot;/sites/onlineplayersassociation.co.uk/files/roulette.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;roulette&quot; title=&quot;roulette&quot; width=&quot;310&quot; height=&quot;200&quot; class=&quot;bigimage&quot; /&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;full_text&quot;&gt;The casino table game of Roulette has been a tradition of the casino parlour network for centuries. The game has always presented itself as a game of daring and a little bit on the cutting edge, and it has traditionally attracted a clientele that is exciting and unafraid.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Roulette – History of Class&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;br&gt;
The game of Roulette has been a favourite of the in-crowd for years. You, of course, remember the traditional James Bond movies that portrayed the image of the entire decade of the 70’s. Every young man wanted to be like Bond, and the era was defined by his flair for expensive amenities and exquisite companions. Bond movies, in which Roger Moore was expertly cast as the man for the ages, pitted Bond against an adversary whose perversity was relentless and whose fatal flaw was an insatiable desire for control.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
The movies were spectacularly staged and acted, and they were box office successes around the world. In nearly every Bond movie, there was a casino scene. In this scene, Bond and his female escort would be dressed to the nines, and the antagonist in the movie would play a part in the scene. Invariably, the scene would take place in an extravagant casino in a luxurious and ritzy setting, such as Morocco. In the blockbuster, Casino Royale, the movie’s theme centres on casino action. In the Bond movies, the casino scene was an integral part of the movie, and the table at which Bond was depicted as playing was the Roulette wheel.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Roulette – The Wheel Has a Mind of Its Own&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;br&gt;
You are probably attracted to the wheel because of the essence of the game. As with Bond, the game of Roulette  not only exudes class and distinction, but it has an aura of light heartedness about it. You are drawn to the Roulette wheel because you are in control of your wagering protocol. You enter the game fortified with chips, and you place the chips on various numbers, colours and patterns in an effort to get on a roll and win big money. As the wheel begins to go ‘round and ‘round, your thoughts drift for a millimetre of a second to James Bond, and, for the flashback instant, you are James Bond, and you can not lose. You have a starlet by your side and, as the wheel starts to slow down, the question in your mind is not if your number will come up, but how much money will you win on this spin. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Your dreams can become reality, even if you are playing the game of Roulette in your home wearing a bathrobe. Let’s face it; all the riches in the world won’t change the spin of the Roulette wheel. The wheel has a mind of its own, and you have as good a chance of winning big money on the wheel as anyone else. So, dream your dreams, and join the millions of others who play the Roulette wheel for fun and entertainment. If you’re looking for the best wheels on the Web, log onto www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk/ for the most reliable and current online casino gambling information available.&lt;/div&gt;</description>
 <category domain="http://www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk/taxonomy/term/11">Roulette</category>
 <category domain="http://www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk/taxonomy/term/264">show in block</category>
 <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2009 11:03:43 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>playtech</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">1990 at http://www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk</guid>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Introduction to Online Slots</title>
 <link>http://www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk/casino/games/online-slots.html</link>
 <description>&lt;img src=&quot;/sites/onlineplayersassociation.co.uk/files/online-slots.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Slots&quot; title=&quot;Slots&quot; width=&quot;310&quot; height=&quot;200&quot; class=&quot;bigimage&quot; /&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;full_text&quot;&gt;Online Slots have replaced the traditional land casinos as the most popular place for slot machine action. The casino gaming industry has always been based on the gambling action of a handful of attractions that players preferred over all others. These are the games that have lured gamblers by the millions into casino parlours worldwide for over a century. While the Poker room has been a favourite among players, and the game of Blackjack has been a preferred play among patrons, the foundation of the casino parlour has always been based on the slot machine action.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Online Slots - Thrill Has Lasted All These Years&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;br&gt;
The Online Slots action has progressed with the technological advancement of the times, and the slots still provide the most drama in the casino parlour for the players. Ever since the machine was invented for enjoyment in the latter part of the 19th Century, the slot machine has provided the most single poignant gambling moment you can find anywhere in the casino. In the traditional casino parlour, the pull of the arm of the slot machine can turn a player’s hopes and dreams into reality, and all within a few seconds of time.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
The fun of the slot machines has transferred into the online gambling casinos where you can get the thrill of a lifetime playing Online Slots with just the click of your computer mouse. Did you ever think that the excitement of slot machine action could be enjoyed within the confines of your own home? Did you ever conceive of the fact that you could win millions just by a click of the mouse of your computer? Well, it is all true! Online Slots are enjoyed daily by millions of people from all over the world as the thrills of the slot machine are brought into homes through the magnificent services of the Internet.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Online Slots - Trust Your Sources&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Before you make a major purchase, whether it is an automobile or a snow blower, isn’t it the wise to consult an expert in the field? Of course, it is the smart thing to do. Experts can advise you on the positive and negative factors associated with your proposed purchase, and they can make recommendations to you regarding your purchase. In much the same way, you should consult an expert in the field of online gambling before investing your hard-earned money on one of these online gambling sites. The most revered of all online gambling portals is the Online Players Association, whose website can be accessed at www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk . The OPA’s affiliates undergo monthly inspections to ensure the players of the finest in casino play online. Before you play Online Slots, consider visiting this bastion of the online gaming industry for a review of the recommended Online Slots sites.&lt;/div&gt;</description>
 <category domain="http://www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk/taxonomy/term/12">Slots</category>
 <category domain="http://www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk/taxonomy/term/264">show in block</category>
 <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2009 10:56:27 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>playtech</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">1988 at http://www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk</guid>
</item>
<item>
 <title>How to Play Online Craps</title>
 <link>http://www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk/casino/games/craps.html</link>
 <description>&lt;img src=&quot;/sites/onlineplayersassociation.co.uk/files/craps.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Craps&quot; title=&quot;Craps&quot; width=&quot;310&quot; height=&quot;200&quot; class=&quot;bigimage&quot; /&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;full_text&quot;&gt;The game of craps is a staple of casino parlours throughout the world. The reason why is that craps just happens to be the most exciting and challenging game in the house. Now, before you log onto the most respected online casino portal on the World Wide Web, the Online Players Association, let me first tell you the craps facts of life. Craps is a game of strategy and luck which can be combined quite often to effect a positive result for your wallet. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Tell me, how many times have you been playing a monotonous and repetitious game in the casino when, all of a sudden, you heard a boisterous yell from a certain part of the casino proper? Being of an inquisitive nature, you walked over to that area from which you heard the noise emanating, and you discovered that the commotion stemmed from a group of players at the craps table.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Craps – Follow the Noise&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;br&gt;
The excitement that surrounds the craps table is contagious. It seems that the most interesting, flamboyant and outgoing players in the casino are attracted to the craps table. Why is that? Well, for one reason, it is the fastest game in the casino. Therefore, people playing the game naturally get caught up in the pace of the action, and their exuberance is displayed by their vocally rooting for a particular outcome on the roll of the dice.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Secondly, there are a great number of different wagers that can take place in a craps game. So, when the dice are rolled, there is a certain degree of finality to the game. A great deal of money can be won or lost with a roll of the dice, and there is a nervousness in the air as the dice are tossed down the craps table. The finality of the roll makes some people winners and some losers, but there is an outcome. If the dice need to be rolled again because there was no determination made on the previous roll, then the craps pot grows larger and the tension builds to a precipitous crescendo as the dice are tossed down the table again. Can you blame those playing the game to be vocally demonstrative as they root that the roll of the dice will be favourable for them?&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Craps – Some Advice for the Novice Player&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;br&gt;
If you are inexperienced in the game of craps and are interested in joining in on the fun and excitement, then listen to some sage advice from a guy who has spent some memorable times at the craps tables in some of the most luxurious hotel/casino complexes in the world. The atmosphere can be quite intimidating for a beginner, so I advise you to play online craps. The play is just as exciting for you personally, and you won’t feel the unnecessary pressure of feeling inadequate in front of more experienced players in the land casinos. You won’t miss the noise at all, and you’ll be gaining experience in the game each time you play. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Also, take advantage of some reputable sites such as www.casinotropez.com; www.gamblingplanet.org; and www.online-casinos.com for information and instruction on the game of craps and for an opportunity to play free games, as well.&lt;/div&gt;</description>
 <category domain="http://www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk/taxonomy/term/38">Craps</category>
 <category domain="http://www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk/taxonomy/term/264">show in block</category>
 <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2009 09:05:17 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>playtech</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">1978 at http://www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk</guid>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Introduction to Online Blackjack</title>
 <link>http://www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk/casino/games/blackjack.html</link>
 <description>&lt;img src=&quot;/sites/onlineplayersassociation.co.uk/files/blackjack.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Blackjack&quot; title=&quot;Blackjack&quot; width=&quot;310&quot; height=&quot;200&quot; class=&quot;bigimage&quot; /&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;full_text&quot;&gt;The game of Blackjack is an easy game to play because the objective is easy for the player to understand. The game is also known as “21” because the object of the game is to get as close to the numerical value of 21 as possible. This objective makes the game simple in nature, and it is the reason why the game of Blackjack can be learned and understood at an early age, and why the game has always been so popular with people of all ages, and throughout the ages.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Blackjack – Know Your Resources&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
A long time ago, an elderly gentleman was winning quite a bit at a Blackjack table when I joined the table. I had been watching him for about twenty minutes and he seemed to be very calm during that period of time. He also built up a large stockpile of chips, so I figured I’d sit next to him and, maybe, some of his good fortune would rub off on me. I sat next to him and greeted him in a friendly manner, and joined the game with three other patrons already deeply engrossed in play. I won; I lost; I won; the older gentleman cashed in his chips. I was shocked that he would leave when he apparently was on a winning streak. As he left the table, I couldn’t help but ask him why he was leaving in the midst of a winning streak? The gentleman turned to me and replied, “Son, know your resources.” This is something that I have never forgotten to this day, some twenty-five years later.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Blackjack - A Game for the Ages&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Those words are as profound today as they were when they were spoken to me. I’ve had more than my share of successes in land casino parlours and, lately, in the online gambling casinos on the Internet.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Over the years, I have always made it a point to know my resources and limitations. The limitations can be a limit on the amount of funds I can wager, or the limitation can come in the form of lack of tacit understanding of the game I was playing. For me, Blackjack was never a game in which I tried to get a set of cards with the numerical value of 21, or as close to 21 as possible. The game of Blackjack, for me, was a contest between myself and the Dealer. I really couldn’t care less what was going on with the other players at the Blackjack table.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
I have succeeded at Blackjack because when I play, I accept the personal challenge of the Dealer. It’s him or me! It is my task to end up with a greater numerical value than the Dealer without going over 21. This is my destiny! I know my resources! When you play Blackjack, make sure you understand those things you can’t control and concentrate on those factors you can control, such as your knowledge of the game including probability factors.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Enjoy playing Blackjack at any of the online casinos certified by the Online Players Association, and best of luck to you!&lt;/div&gt;</description>
 <category domain="http://www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk/taxonomy/term/9">Blackjack</category>
 <category domain="http://www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk/taxonomy/term/264">show in block</category>
 <category domain="http://www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk/taxonomy/term/296">show on frontpage</category>
 <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2009 08:12:40 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>playtech</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">1972 at http://www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk</guid>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Online Backgammon Rules </title>
 <link>http://www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk/casino/games/backgammon-rules.html</link>
 <description>&lt;img src=&quot;/sites/onlineplayersassociation.co.uk/files/backgammon-rules.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Online Backgammon Rules&quot; title=&quot;Online Backgammon Rules&quot; width=&quot;310&quot; height=&quot;200&quot; class=&quot;bigimage&quot; /&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;full_text&quot;&gt;The game of Backgammon has a long and storied history dating back some 5000 years to ancient Egyptian times, long before the comic Steve Martin immortalised the inimitable figure from ancient Egypt, King Tut. The game made its way from Rome to Persia to Europe over the course of some 2000 years before the rules of the game were officially written and edited by the Englishman, Edmund Hoyle, in the middle of the 18th Century. The game has not changed perceptibly since then, except for the addition of the doubling cube manoeuvre which interjected some American spice to the game in the first quarter of the 20th Century. Today, the game is featured in gambling casino websites all over the Internet. The online Backgammon rules allow players to test their skills in an online venue where they play for pay.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Online Backgammon Rules - Movements Like the Game of Checkers&lt;br&gt;
The online Backgammon rules are based on the old military precept of seek and destroy. There is only one ultimate winner in the game of Backgammon, and it is the player who employs this military philosophy in his or her game regimen who will survive and win. The game of Backgammon can be decided in a matter of minutes or it can take as long as twenty minutes to complete. The game can be determined by reaching and accumulating a certain amount of points, which shortens the length of the game.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
The game of Backgammon resembles the game of Checkers in its form, playing surface, and movement and shape of the game pieces. The object of the game is to move your pieces past your opponent’s pieces and place them in your inner board and then “bear off” your pieces. You bear off your game pieces by manoeuvres initiated by a roll of two dice that remove your pieces from the board. There are tracks of 12 triangles on each side of the playing surface, and these triangles have point values. Since there are 24 triangles, the point values range from 1 point up to 24.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
The online Backgammon rules set up your pieces in this fashion:  Two checkers on point #24; five checkers on point #13; three checkers on point #8; and five checker pieces on point #6. The opponent’s pieces are arranged on his area of the board in precisely the same way. The game is predicated on movement based on the results of the rolls of the dice, and you can land in spaces that are empty and have no point value, a point occupied by your own piece or a point occupied by your opponent. These results set off a series of consequences as you gain points while you attempt to move your pieces to the home side of the board.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
If you are interested in learning more about the fascinating game of Backgammon and understanding the online Backgammon rules, don’t hesitate to log on to the Internet’s most respected authority on gambling on the Internet, the Online Players Association, which can be accessed at www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk . This portal will give you information on how to play the game of Backgammon online, and on the best online gambling websites that feature Backgammon play. These websites allow you to play Backgammon for free until you have enough experience and confidence to match your skills for pay in the online casino of your choice.&lt;/div&gt;</description>
 <category domain="http://www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk/taxonomy/term/171">Backgammon</category>
 <category domain="http://www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk/taxonomy/term/264">show in block</category>
 <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2009 07:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>playtech</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">1969 at http://www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk</guid>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Baccarat History </title>
 <link>http://www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk/casino/games/baccarat-history.html</link>
 <description>&lt;img src=&quot;/sites/onlineplayersassociation.co.uk/files/baccarat-history.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;baccarat history&quot; title=&quot;baccarat history&quot; width=&quot;310&quot; height=&quot;200&quot; class=&quot;bigimage&quot; /&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;full_text&quot;&gt;The game of Baccarat has been misunderstood for centuries.  Baccarat history has been surrounded by mystery and intrigue ever since it was invented by a group of French aristocrats in the mid 1500’s.  As the story goes, these Frenchmen chose to decide the fate of a young virgin on the luck of a playing card.  If an eight or nine was thrown down, the young lady would become a member of the aristocracy; if a six or seven was turned up on the table, then she could no longer participate in one of her favourite activities, observing religious functions; if a card with a value of less than six was displayed, then she would be sent out to “swim with the fishes.”   Thus, the first chapter in Baccarat history had been written.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Folklore has it that a nine was turned up, and she became the great, great grandmother of Marie Antoinette, who knew a thing or two about how to treat peasants.  But that is for another time.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Baccarat History in the Making&lt;br&gt;
You can see that the noble history of the game of Baccarat still has maintained its heritage.  The game flourished in different European countries over the next few centuries and different variations of the original game sprang up. However, the game of Baccarat, as we know it today, is a variation of the original French “Chemin de fer” and is popular throughout the European countries as well as in America. Over time, a number of varied cultures have contributed to the history of Baccarat.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
My Very Own Baccarat History&lt;br&gt;
When I joined a Baccarat table for the first time, all my fears and trepidations went out the window.  Sure, there were people at the table who looked like they had more money than I have, and they certainly were dressed more stylishly and upscale.  Let me tell you that the guy next to me had on a polo shirt wit the inscription, “Kiss my A...”  The people could not have been any nicer to me, and even congratulated me when I won four hands in a row.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
A Rich Baccarat History Indeed&lt;br&gt;
Over the years, the game of Baccarat has become synonymous with the rich and famous, and the game for high rollers.  If you had to guess what table a movie star was playing, you’d be correct most of the time if you said the Baccarat table.  Big rollers are attracted to the Baccarat tables for two main reasons.  First, the game was invented by the aristocracy for the aristocracy, and remnants of that tradition have remained part of the Baccarat history over the years.  The second reason is that limitations on maximum bets can be raised by the house at any time.  This has wide appeal to the high rollers of the world.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Online Baccarat is Catching On&lt;br&gt;
Of course, if you enjoy gambling in your undies, as I often do, then online casino gambling is the way to go.  Believe me, the dealer online won’t give a darn what you’re wearing.  In fact, Baccarat history has added a new chapter as the game has taken off in popularity over the past several months.  If you’re looking for a good Baccarat site, my advice is to consult with the Online Players association on the web at www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk/.  The OPA is the recognized online gambling authority and has client facilitators available to help you find a suitable site.&lt;/div&gt;</description>
 <category domain="http://www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk/taxonomy/term/10">Baccarat</category>
 <category domain="http://www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk/taxonomy/term/264">show in block</category>
 <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2009 06:57:51 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>playtech</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">1963 at http://www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk</guid>
</item>
<item>
 <title>An Introduction to Online Baccarat</title>
 <link>http://www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk/casino/games/baccarat.html</link>
 <description>&lt;img src=&quot;/sites/onlineplayersassociation.co.uk/files/baccarat.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Baccarat&quot; title=&quot;Baccarat&quot; width=&quot;310&quot; height=&quot;200&quot; class=&quot;bigimage&quot; /&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;full_text&quot;&gt;On my last visit to a land casino parlour, I made it a point to visit the area of the Baccarat tables.  It was for me more than slightly peculiar, because the tables were not located in the main casino table game area.  There were plenty of people milling around the various tables such as Poker in its many variations, Roulette, Sic Bo, Craps, and Blackjack.  Unfortunately, there wasn’t a Baccarat table to be seen. Still, the casino was buzzing with excitement as I scoured the floor for the game of my particular interest that day; Baccarat.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
In Search of Baccarat&lt;br&gt;
As I entered the lavish room, I saw 3 men sitting at a table at the head of the room.  Glancing quickly from table to table, I noticed that some Baccarat tables were surrounded by very well-dressed patrons, and other tables had regularly dressed patrons, neat and clean but not dressed to the nines.  I approached the table where the 3 supervisors were sitting, and asked their permission to walk around the room.  I so badly wished to play but had not yet mustered the courage to join a table.  So, I walked around the room and noticed that the patrons seemed very relaxed, even at those tables where the minimums were quite high.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
My Baccarat Introduction&lt;br&gt;
There was one table with a very high minimum that had no players at the table.  Mmmm! I wonder why!  Finally, I talked myself into joining a table at which the patrons seemed extremely comfortable.  It was at this table on a Tuesday afternoon in the fall of the year that my Baccarat introduction took place.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
The dealer was extremely helpful and assisted me through the entire process of the game.  You see, the game looks stuffy and a might complicated, because many of the patrons who play Baccarat are dressed impressively.  However, there was no arrogance that I could detect at my table, and I had a marvellous experience.  So marvellous, in fact, the first thing I did the next morning was go online and search for an online Baccarat site.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Within 10 minutes I’d already found plenty to choose from and selected the one that looked the most reliable; Casino Tropez. What I didn’t know at the time was that this particular online casino just happened to also be one of the best, if not THE best, gambling website on the Net. Evidently, my good luck had already begun.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Online Baccarat - It’s a Whole New Game&lt;br&gt;
Naturally, being a newcomer to playing Baccarat, I was a little worried (just a little, mind you) that perhaps the online version of this classic game would differ from its land casino counterpart. But low and behold, everything was suddenly wonderfully familiar. Plus, the site provided all sorts of rules, strategies, tutorials and tips on how to play Baccarat (to my heart’s content).&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
So, if you’re looking for some classy fun-filled action, but not into the whole Mister Dress-Up thing, online Baccarat is definitely your best bet.&lt;/div&gt;</description>
 <category domain="http://www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk/taxonomy/term/10">Baccarat</category>
 <category domain="http://www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk/taxonomy/term/264">show in block</category>
 <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2009 06:53:17 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>playtech</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">1962 at http://www.onlineplayersassociation.co.uk</guid>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
